This is how I'll become.
Supreme Commander!
A hero!
This is my story!
Let's go.
I've always seen my dreams.
It's not so high that I can't.
It's not so much that I wanted to be.
That's when you were me.
I was always connected.
I don't want to go in front of
you, I want to go in front of you.
I'll go in front of you.
I'll go in front of this world.
I'll connect with you.
To be
continued...
I heard a rumor that the 7th
Squadron's second-in-command
fainted when she was attacked
by one of the humanoid Shuki.
How pathetic!
You're determined to drag the Azuma family's
reputation through the mud, aren't you?
Give it up and come home already.
But to be fair, those
Shuki aren't exactly weak.
The 3rd Squadron had a
run-in with them too.
Not just once, but two times.
Strength in numbers.
Us working together would be smart.
We find your presence at battle
reassuring, Commander Kyoka.
But some of us are a little hesitant
to put our trust in your entire team.
I won't name any names.
But we're concerned that her
impotence might slow us down.
We need to assess the current
capabilities of each of our teams.
How about we hold an inter-squad
Mato exhibition match?
Oh? Huh?
A Mato exhibition match?
What is this, a baseball league?
An exhibition match is
what we call a contest
of strength and skill
between two squadrons.
That makes sense.
Does single combat sound acceptable?
You have never been the type
to mince words, have you, Kyo?
Fine by me we'll adjust
our numbers accordingly.
See you later, little slave!
Commander, I have a request.
Will you help me prepare
for the exhibition?
Huh?
It's going to be physically demanding.
I'll do whatever it
takes to win the match!
Then you'd better buckle down
and start training, right?
Uh?
You heard the commander!
I himity azuma claim you as
my slave from here on out!
Yuki's ramen broth is delicious.
I know it's so good!
I always end up eating
too much of his cooking.
Did you use some sort
of secret ingredient?
I wanted it to be rich
and thick this time, so...
I tried adding chicken fat.
Your skills are perfect for a slave if
you're good at cleaning and cooking.
Would you please remind me again how I
got roped into being your slave, too?
It's for the sake of the
motto exhibition match.
It's absolutely imperative that I win.
But that doesn't explain why
I'm being forced to be your...
Keeping it simple this
time with single combat.
So your sister's attitude
struck a nerve, didn't it?
Now you can use this match
as an excuse to kick her ass.
Thank you for the chance
to do some ass kicking!
Ass-kicking is your new job!
Oh, I'll kick it, all right!
What's with all the kicking of asses?!
You still haven't answered my question.
Why am I your slave now?
Transforming parts of my body into
weapons isn't my main ability.
I only use it because
it's compatible. Huh?
This is my real technique.
Miss Kyoka?
It looks like some sort
of trading card game.
Learning.
I can learn other people's
abilities and use them for myself.
That's my specialty.
Isn't that ability super OP?
I select someone's talents that I want
to use on my phone and implement it.
What that means is, I can
use the commanders now.
You do understand what Miss Kyoka's
ability entails, right? Yeah, yeah.
I'm aware it's physically demanding.
I got this, okay?
I don't mind taking
over the cleaning or the
laundry if it means I get
to kick Yachiho's ass.
We're surrounded by Shuuki! Hurry up!
Okay, fine, but I warned you!
You're in a different shape
than when the commander does it.
I can move with lightning speed
faster than with Miss Kyoka.
But the drawback is
that I'm not as strong.
Well, in that case...
I'll just beat on them till they drop!
This is the key to fighting my sister!
You could pick from any number of abilities
tell me why you insist on this one?
It gives you a chance
to be useful even though
you're a man if anything
you ought to be great!
This is the price of her ability.
Huh?
So, by physically demanding,
she really meant...
Wait, how come I can't
control my body movement?
Well, it's because my
reward isn't over yet.
But, why does your reward have to be this?
Speaking of which, quit cocking
at me already, you perv.
I would, but if I do that, you might...
On second thought, just see for yourself.
I thought so.
Look, it's the price of her ability,
so it won't stop until I get my reward.
Is this a sufficient
enough reward for you?
How indecent!
You would be better off
using a different ability.
Look, I would if I could, okay?
Believe me.
So shameful.
Wait, but why can't you?
There's a compatibility
component to learning.
It degrades the quality of most abilities
to the point they become useless.
For example,
if I were to use Shushu's Paradigm Shift,
all it would do is increase my bus
size by about three centimeters.
Okay, but the price of
Miss Kyoka's ability is...
I'm aware of that, okay?
Why are you so desperate to win this?
I'm from the Azuma household,
an influential family with
major accomplishments in Mato.
My older sisters are successful, so
everyone had high hopes for me too.
But I'd overexert myself before
a big event and get hurt,
or I'd get nervous and
come down with a fever.
I never had any results to show for it.
Yeah, story of my life.
Same with my Peach ability.
I'm guessing they noticed the
problem you mentioned earlier?
Because of that, I'd always get teased
whenever I couldn't keep up with my sisters.
I see.
It must have been tough
for you growing up.
This is my first chance
since I cut ties with
the Azuma family to prove
them wrong about me.
So you are going to help
me and be happy about it!
It's really hard to want to help someone
when they can't even ask politely.
As for my ultimate goal, I want
to be a hero like the Commander.
I feel like I'll become a better version
of myself if I can beat Yachi-ho.
That part of me that nobody's ever
seen deserves a proper chance to shine.
She's just like me.
Still, we're missing something for
the exhibition match. What's that?
A finishing move that
will demolish our enemy.
Come to think of it,
all I've done so far is mindlessly
punch and kick everything in sight.
I have my own reasons for
wanting to get stronger.
Maybe she's the key to opening
up a new door for me, too.
Even better if I manage
to help Miss Kyoka.
Okay, fine.
I'll do whatever you want.
Watch your attitude.
You're my slave, remember?
You don't have the right to refuse.
Yeah, sure.
Can you tell me what Yachiho's ability is?
It's golden hour.
She can control time, including
freezing it and rewinding it.
Well, we're screwed.
My ears are burning I have a
sneaking suspicion Himari is talking
about me right now Oh Himari
such a worthless little brat it's
only right that she does my bidding
for the Rest of her miserable
life I'm going to put her in her
place at the exhibition match
I can't wait for the big day to arrive
Yachi-ho's ability is dangerous
for sure, but it takes power.
She'll get tired if she uses it too
many times, and that's how we'll win.
The fact that she can use it more
than once makes things tricky, though.
Also, she strikes a very odd
pose to trigger her ability.
It's a routine that emphasizes her skills.
Hmm.
So then we'll have to
beat her to the punch.
In that case, we ought to take advantage
of my speed for our finishing move.
Exactly.
An ultra-fast maneuver that won't
give her a chance to freeze time.
And no leeway to rewind time either.
An attack with enough force to knock
her out of the fight completely.
So, like, a swift step
forward into a head-on punch.
I think that would be fastest.
Let's polish it into a
deadly blow she can't dodge.
I want you to try channeling all your
strength into a single part of your body.
Hmm.
Channel.
All my strength to my legs!
It worked!
Whoa, you actually did it!
Just in time for our
practice dummies to arrive.
Hell yeah!
I'm even faster than before.
At this rate, we're golden!
Wait, why didn't it work?
My lower half is exhausted.
You probably lost most
of your arm strength
because you poured all
your energy into your legs.
Instead, we'll keep experimenting with
it until we perfect your technique.
Uh, is this my reward?
Wow, he does look different than
when he's with me, commander?
Miss Kyoka, keep it up! Roger! Smart.
Channeling his strength into a single body
part to produce a more powerful effect.
It's a proactive approach.
You've got a knack for this.
Gee, thank you, Commander.
That being said, why are you
watching him from way back here?
Well, I...
You mustn't forget the fundamental
essence of my ability. Its essence?
Make me proud.
Hey!
I'll be riding you during the exhibition.
Let's do this like it's the real deal.
This ability requires dominating a slave,
not just standing back and coaching.
Get on top of him.
Seize the slave's chains and
command him as his master.
Channel all your strength into your legs.
That's strange.
I feel more power flowing
through me this time.
Go crush that Shuki!
Whoa, did I really just do that?
A foolproof finishing move!
I got lost in the moment.
I'm not sure if I can replicate
that. Oh, don't worry.
Mato has plenty of
practice dummies to use.
I'm a million times more
worn out than usual.
Your technique lacks precision sometimes.
We need to practice and
develop consistency.
Your clothes are...
Look, it's the price of her ability, okay?
I swear.
Indecent.
Bring it on, Shuki!
I'm gonna master this technique so I
can put it into use again in the future!
That's the spirit, Yuki.
Let's go.
I feel good that's great,
but once the exhibition is done
the Himariyuki duel will be over.
I guess so after all he
belongs to the commander
not me and it's a physically
demanding ability.
For now let's focus on today the whole
demon defense force will know who won.
And the outcome will affect our
squadrons the commander's reputation.
We've got to put our
best foot forward. Right!
Both for myself and the commander,
since she organized this.
I can't lose!
That reminds me, aren't the other members
of the Six Squadron supposed to show up?
Huh?
Hello!
We got here a little early,
so I came to de-stress.
Since when was she in the Six Squadron?
That's Sahara Wakasam.
She's a homebody, so it's rare to
see her out and about like this.
And now she's asleep? How funny!
She's certainly got guts, doesn't she?
Go ahead without me.
You'll do great, Himari.
Don't sweat it.
Taking a bath before the exhibition match?
You must be feeling awfully confident.
I intend to be clean and
well-groomed when I win today.
Oh, yeah?
It sounds like you've got a plan in mind.
But the question is, can
you actually pull it off?
Of course!
I know I can!
Oh, you still haven't left the dorm?
The match is supposed to start soon.
You're only delaying the inevitable.
It'll be okay.
Hey, remember, we trained our asses off.
Awfully cocky for a slave. What?
Well, obviously, we're guaranteed to win.
Hey, everyone.
Sorry we're late.
Write your name down.
What's this for?
It's used to trigger
Gina Beezin's ability.
She can create a barrier by drawing a line
on the ground that acts as a boundary.
Only those who sign their
names can enter the barrier.
Also, any damage sustained during combat
inside the barrier will be healed.
Thank you for your patience.
My name's Gina Bizen of the 10th Squadron,
and I'll be your rep for today's
Inner Squad Exhibition Match.
Gina's Club!
This ability of mine is
like a dream come true.
I get to see the demon defense
force up close and personal.
Not everyone believes
Peach's cramped power
is based on the person's
nature and knowledge,
but I totally do.
This barrier could withstand
the force of a thousand Shuki.
We're counting on you to judge this fight.
Right, Lady Ten and Lady Kyo?
I will do my best!
Lady Kyo?
Are you a fangirl or something?
Huh? Oh, God.
I really need to shut the hell up.
All right, I'm all set!
Uh, did you make that?
Nei counts as a non-combatant, so
her job is to cheer on her teammates!
First up in round one!
Himari Azuma of the seventh squadron
versus Yachiho Azuma of the sixth squadron!
The rules are whoever gives up
or gets knocked out first loses!
Injuries will be healed,
so feel free to go nuts!
As soon as I humiliate you, I'm
going to drag you back home.
Then you'll be my special little servant.
I'm not the same person I was back then.
I will defeat you, Yachi-ho.
As part of my ability,
he's going to assist me.
Fine by me.
Denying a dog handler her
pup is just plain heartless.
Is everyone ready?
Now let the first match begin!
Don't say I didn't warn you.
You won't last a second again.
Where the hell did that come from?
Um, golden hour!
Rewind, five seconds!
Beacon!
She's tired.
We planned ahead in case we couldn't
beat her with a single blow.
Let's stick to our strategy.
She changed tactics.
Was it an accident or
did she do it on purpose?
Oh, Himari, you haven't realized
my ability has gotten stronger.
It's an indisputable fact that little
sisters can't beat big sisters.
I'll prove it to you with prime time!
Thank you.
The heart of you is being told to
hear from the heart of your heart.
One, two,
three, four, The heart of
the heart is being moved.
The heart of the heart is being moved.
You can see that you're holding on.
You're holding on.
You're being sad.
I won't be able to leave it.
pay or she can't switch out
for a different skill later.
Every technique used
requires lots of studying.
It's the perfect skill for
someone like Miss Himari.